ineedhits.com 2003-12-06

# Privacy Policy [ineedhits.com]

|    
Advertise your website below for 1 cent or less per banner display   
  
Click the banner above to be transferred to our client's website   
|  |  | _**_**

**_**_  
---|---  

[](https://www.truste.org/validate/12312) |  We at ineedhits.com [Ineedhits.com Pty Ltd] pride ourselves on attention to detail regarding our customers’ privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our   
Privacy Policy.  
---|---  
  
ineedhits.com [Ineedhits.com Pty Ltd] is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. 

This privacy statement covers the site [www.ineedhits.com]. Because this Web Site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users’ privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

  1. What personally identifiable information does ineedhits.com collect?

  2. What organization/s collects the information?

  3. With whom ineedhits.com may share user information?

  4. How ineedhits.com uses the information?

  5. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?

  6. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under ineedhits.com control?

  7. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

  8. What happens if our Privacy Policy changes?

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact our Webmaster by emailing to [webmaster@ineedhits.com](mailto:webmaster@ineedhits.com). If users do not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact TRUSTe through the [TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process](http://www.truste.org/users/watchdog.html) TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web Site to resolve users concerns. 

**Q1:** **What personally identifiable information does ineedhits.com  
      collect?**

This Privacy Policy covers http://www.ineedhits.com treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected by our company when a customer is visiting our site and using our services. This policy also covers ineedhits.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that business partner’s share with our company and added to our Web Site database. This policy does not apply to he practices of companies that ineedhits.com does not own or control, or to people that ineedhits.com does ot employ or manage.

To place an order on our Web Site, a user must first complete an order form. Whilst placing an order, a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have shown as an interest.

top

**Q2:** ** What organization/s collects the information?**

ineedhits.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web Site and co-branded partner Web Sites. We will not sell, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. When the user signs up for these services, we may share names, or other contact information that is necessary for third parties to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

top **Q3:** ** With whom ineedhits.com may share user information?**

**SHARING:**  
ineedhits.com share personal information with third parties who we use to perform functions on our behalf. For example, we use a third party (Camtech Corporation) to verify and process your credit card information in order for us to bill you for requested services. All third parties are contractually obligated to use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is given. 

When registering your Web Site to 300+ Search Engines, most require us to provide **minimal** personal information such as your…

* Your full name
* Company name (if applicable)
* Country
*  **Contact email**  
     We do not provide your personal email address in this service.   
     We consider your **“personal”** contact email as confidential and   
     kept **'entirely private'**. We only use your personal email address   
     for our technicians to send service reports or notifications to you…

We create a special FREE email account to ensure our customer's privacy. This FREE email account is for you to store the emails (over time some 20-300+ confirmations) that the Search Engines send notifying you that they have received your "Customer and Web Site Registration Details", and that your Web Site is now cued for indexing into their database.

Bigmailbox.com hosts the free email account, which has been specially co-branded for ineedhits.com.

When registering your Web Site through our co-branded Inktomi Search/Submit service, we only provide the Web Page/s (URLs) subscribed for inclusion into the Inktomi Search Engine database. 

We may also disclose your personal information when required by law or in the our belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to acts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our main Web Site or co-branded partner Web Sites'.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES:**  
ineedhits.com and its co-branded Web Sites’ contain links to other sites. Please be aware that ineedhits.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web Site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on our Web Sites.

top

**Q4:** **How ineedhits.com uses the information?**

**COOKIES AND LOG FILES:**   
First, we use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign identification to your computer. The unique user ID contained within your cookie automatically identifies your computer, but not you, to our servers every time you visit our site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user but may be correlated with identity information in our log files. You can turn the cookies feature off by using your browser's preference options, but you may not be able to utilize some services properly. 

Second, we keep track of your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information about you, such as your location and your Internet service provider. ineedhits.com may also collect combined information on how our users are utilizing the site. This might include information regarding traffic patterns through the site and search queries. 

Third, we log browser types, access times, URLs from which visitors came to our site and URLs viewed by visitors while on our site. Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not provide this information to third parties, except in combined form.

top

**Q5:** **What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and      distribution of the information?**

**ORDERS:**  
We request information from the user on our order forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and email address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to orders. If we have trouble when processing an order, this contact information is used to contact the user.

**NEWSLETTER Opt-In AND Opt-Out:**  
Upon ordering various services from us, customers will receive an email notification from Yahoo! Groups requesting them whether they wish to Opt-In to subscribed to our Web Site Promotion Tips newsletter. If a customer does not wish to be part of our complimentary newsletter subscription list after they have accepted, they have the option to Opt-Out at any time by following the instructions on our Web Site at…

www.ineedhits.com/news/ or www.ineedhits.com/news/unsubscribe.asp

top

**Q6:** **What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss,  
     misuse or alteration of information under ineedhits.com control?**

**SECURITY:**  
Our Web Site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web Site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounts department or our customer service representatives, or our Website technicians) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Our servers that store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment and are stored behind a firewall.

If you have any questions about the security at our Web Site, you can send an email to [](mailto:webmaster@ineedhits.com)[webmaster@ineedhits.com. ](mailto:webmaster@ineedhits.com)

[](mailto:webmaster@ineedhits.com)top

**Q7:** **How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.**

All users of our co-branded Inktomi Search/Submit service can review and modify their account or profile information on the site at [ink.ineedhits.com/secure/login.asp](http://ink.ineedhits.com/secure/login.asp) . Alternatively they can also contact us by email through several avenues provided on pages of our www.ineedhits.com Web Site or directly email us with the customer support links provided in our service report emails. 

top

**Q8:** **What happens if our Privacy Policy changes?**

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES:**   
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, our users will be notified so they are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way on an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if you have deleted/deactivated your personal information you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. We will only use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

To place an order select the various offers below: 

  * Submit PRO
  * Submit ONGOING - Monthly
  * Ultimate Platinum Package - Monthly
  * Gold Package.
  * Silver Package.
  * Bronze Package.
  * Newsletter Sponsorship.
  * Banner Advertising.

Return to ineedhits.com homepage.

Advertise your web site below for 1 cent or less per banner display   
  
Click the banner above to be transferred to our client's website   

ineedhits.com "Driving Visitors (hits) to Your Web Site"  
ineedhits, ineedhits.com, and their designs, logos, and  
related marks are trademarks of Ineedhits.com Pty Ltd.  
© Copyright 2003 ineedhits.com
